<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Blackity - News</title>
    <link>https://blackity.store/blogs/news</link>
    <description>Latest news and updates from Blackity Store</description>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Fathers Day</title>
      <link>https://blackity.store/blogs/news/happy-fathers-day</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blackity.store/blogs/news/happy-fathers-day</guid>
      <description>
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0699/3903/6225/files/ChatGPT_Image_Apr_27_2025_12_33_55_PM.png?v=1768613476" alt=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:31:44 +0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dad love handwriting gift</title>
      <link>https://blackity.store/blogs/news/dad-love-handwriting-gift</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blackity.store/blogs/news/dad-love-handwriting-gift</guid>
      <description>
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0699/3903/6225/files/handwriting-image-feature-text-tell-about-the-love-of-a-daughter-to-father-background-is-vintage-color-decorate-around-with-gnomes.png?v=1768612187" alt="handwriting image feature text tell about the love of a daughter to father, background is vintage color. decorate around with gnomes"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:10:55 +0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Dad Joke Ever dude</title>
      <link>https://blackity.store/blogs/news/best-dad-joke-ever-dude</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blackity.store/blogs/news/best-dad-joke-ever-dude</guid>
      <description>
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0699/3903/6225/files/Gemini_Generated_Image_unfjvpunfjvpunfj.png?v=1768349457" alt=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you ready to roll your eyes and groan? Get ready for a collection of dad jokes that will have you laughing (or cringing) in no time. Dads are known for their cheesy sense of humor, and these quotes are no exception. So sit back, relax, and prepare yourself for some serious dad joke action!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why did the scarecrow win an award?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because he was outstanding in his field! Classic dad humor right there. You can always count on a dad to come up with a punny joke like this. It's corny, but you can't help but chuckle a little, right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What do you call fake spaghetti?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An impasta! Dad jokes are all about the wordplay, and this one is a prime example. It's so bad that it's good. You can't help but appreciate the effort that goes into crafting these puns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why couldn't the bicycle stand up by itself?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because it was two tired! Ah, the classic dad joke formula: take a common phrase or situation and add a pun to it. It's simple yet effective. You may groan at first, but deep down, you know you love it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How does a penguin build its house?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Igloos it together! Dad jokes often involve animals, puns, and a healthy dose of silliness. This one is no exception. It's cute, quirky, and guaranteed to make you crack a smile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why did the math book look sad?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because it had too many problems. Dad jokes don't discriminate – they cover all subjects, including math. This one may make you groan, but you secretly appreciate the cleverness behind it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So there you have it – a collection of dad jokes that will have you laughing, groaning, and rolling your eyes all at the same time. Whether you love them or hate them, you can't deny the charm of a good old dad joke. So go ahead, share these quotes with your friends and family, and spread the dad joke love!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
    </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 07:34:52 +0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sibling Rivalry dad love</title>
      <link>https://blackity.store/blogs/news/sibling-rivalry-dad-love</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blackity.store/blogs/news/sibling-rivalry-dad-love</guid>
      <description>
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0699/3903/6225/files/ChatGPT_Image_Apr_27_2025_01_05_07_PM.png?v=1768314831" alt=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Family love, huh? It's like a rollercoaster ride - full of ups, downs, twists, and turns. But hey, isn't that what makes it so darn exciting? Let's dive into the wild world of family love and all its quirks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What's the Deal with Sibling Rivalry?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, sibling rivalry, the age-old tale of brothers and sisters fighting over who gets the last slice of pizza. But deep down, it's all just a big ol' love fest. Because let's face it, who else can you share inside jokes with that go way back to childhood?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why Do Parents Always Know Best?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parents, the ultimate know-it-alls (or so they think). They may drive you crazy with their advice, but at the end of the day, they just want what's best for you. Plus, who else will embarrass you with baby photos at your graduation party?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How Does Family Love Keep You Grounded?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Family love is like your anchor in a stormy sea. They keep you grounded when life gets a little too crazy. Whether it's a hug from mom or a pep talk from dad, family love has a magical way of making everything okay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why Are Family Traditions So Important?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Family traditions are like the secret sauce that makes your family unique. Whether it's Grandma's famous apple pie recipe or the annual family camping trip, these traditions bind you together and create memories that last a lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Can You Choose Your Family?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
    </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:36:32 +0700</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>